Guide to GMU Public Relations Press Releases
Copyright George Mason University Libraries
- GMU Public Relations- Press Releases
  - CHEMISTRY CLUB ROADSHOW. (Box Box 20)
  - LECTURE SERIES FRONTIERS IN DATA COMMUNICATIONS. (Box Box 20)
  - NATIONAL TEACHER EXAM CHANGES. (Box Box 20)
  - POETRY READING - COLLINS L. RECTOR. (Box Box 20)
  - HAZEL ELECTED RECTOR OF B.D OF VISITOR. (Box Box 20)
  - EQUIPMENT FOR THE DISABLED DONATED TO GMU. (Box Box 20)
  - VA CANDIDATES TO SPEAK AT GMU. (Box Box 20)
  - GEMS CONTRIBUTED TO GEORGE DEPT - EVERHART JEWELERS. (Box Box 20)
  - GMU CHORUS CASE CONVOCATION. (Box Box 20)
  - GMU'S PRE - SCHOOL OPEN HOUSE. (Box Box 20)
  - "SIGNALS DANCE CONCERT. (Box Box 20)
  - FOREIGN FILM FESTIVAL. (Box Box 20)
  - SUMMER WRITING INSTITUTE COMMUNITY. (Box Box 20)
  - GMU SUMMER ORCHESTRA CONCERT. (Box Box 20)
  - SYMPHONIC CHORAL SUMMER CONCERT. (Box Box 20)
  - REFRESHER COURSE NURSES. (Box Box 20)
  - ECONOMIC CHAIR ENDOWMENT. (Box Box 20)
  - "OPEN P.T. MINING" DISCUSSED AT GMU. (Box Box 20)
  - "INSTANT POETRY" METRO GALLERY J.D. SERPICO. (Box Box 20)
  - CALLING ALL SINGERS - AUDITION. (Box Box 20)
  - NEW DOCTORAL PROGRAM IN BIOLOGY / PUBLIC POLICIES. (Box Box 20)
  - SOUTH AFRICA RECEPTION. (Box Box 20)
  - FACULTY ART EXHIBIT. (Box Box 20)
  - INDIAN DANCE RECITAL. (Box Box 20)
  - PEDIATRIC REVIEW COURSE. (Box Box 20)
  - JUAN RULFO. (Box Box 20)
  - LITERARY SEASON BEGINS D. ST. JOHN AND E. SPIRES. (Box Box 20)
  - BARBERSHOP CHORUS CONCERT. (Box Box 20)
  - HIGH SCHOOL DEBATE CLINIC. (Box Box 20)
  - EXERCISE PROGRAM FOR OLDER ADULTS. (Box Box 20)
  - MUSIC PREMIER - STEPHEN BURTON. (Box Box 20)
  - BENEFIT ART AUCTION. (Box Box 20)
  - DR. DAVID LIVINGSTON DISCUSSED DNA AND GENETIC ENGINEERING. (Box Box 20)
  - MAJORS AND CAREERS PUBLICATION. (Box Box 20)
  - GMU APPTS. COORDINATOR OF DISABLED STUD. SERVICES. (Box Box 20)
  - GMU'S SECOND DECADE LAUNCHED AT COMMENCEMENT. (Box Box 20)
  - ENGLISH LANGUAGE INSTITUTE SUMMER SESSION. (Box Box 20)
  - OPERATION - BIO - CHEMIST STUDENT TAUBENBERGER. (Box Box 20)
  - CENTER FOR PUBLIC CHOICE MOVES TO GMU. (Box Box 20)
  - GMU FORENSICS TEAM 5TH IN NATION. (Box Box 20)
  - JULIAN STEIN, GMU PROF. RECEIVES AALR AWARD. (Box Box 20)
  - SUMMER SINGING AT GMU. (Box Box 20)
  - GMU PRESIDENT JOHNSON GRADUATION SPEECH. (Box Box 20)
  - GMU APPOINTS NEW PUBLIC RELATIONS SERVICES DIR. (Box Box 20)
  - ACADEMIC AFFAIRS U.P. APPOINTED. (Box Box 20)
  - PROP. TO REVOLUTIONIZE GENERAL EDUCATION. (Box Box 20)
  - AUDITION FOR SUMMER ORCHESTRA. (Box Box 20)
  - RAISING MONEY FOR PUBLIC BROADCASTING. (Box Box 20)
  - GM FOUNDATION FUND RAISING. (Box Box 20)
  - SEMINAR ON Caribbean. (Box Box 20)
  - JEAN CHEF - PHOTOGRAPHS FROM AROUND WORLD. (Box Box 20)
  - GMU OFFERS NEW DANCE DEGREE. (Box Box 20)
  - ALUMNI ASSOC. SETS ANNUAL MEETING. (Box Box 20)
  - CIVIL WAR INSTITUTE. (Box Box 20)
  - CHAMBER MUSIC. (Box Box 20)
  - FLEXIBLE SCHEDULING AT GMU THIS YEAR. (Box Box 20)
  - SUMMER WRITING INSTITUTE. (Box Box 20)
  - PROSEMINAR - ALP K. WHITE PERCEPTION IN INT'L CONFLICT. (Box Box 20)
  - OLGA DALPERIN - ARGENTINIAN PIANIST AT GMU. (Box Box 20)
  - ART SALE. (Box Box 20)
  - PRO - SEMINAR FAMILY LAW, DIVORCE MEDIATION. (Box Box 20)
  - SYMPHONIC WINDS IN CONCERT. (Box Box 20)
  - CHAMBER ORCHESTRA PERFORMS AT GMU. (Box Box 20)
  - GMU HOSTS HIGH SCHOOL MATH COMPETITION. (Box Box 20)
  - EFFECTS OF COMPUTER ON SOCIETY. (Box Box 20)
  - ECONOMIC PROBLEMS OF SOCIALISM DISCUSSED. (Box Box 20)
  - BIOLOGY FACULTY PUBLISHES BOOK. (Box Box 20)
  - CAN DOCTORS PLAY GOD. (Box Box 20)
  - NURSING REFRESHER COURSE. (Box Box 20)
  - COUNCIL ON ENVIRONMENT HEARING. (Box Box 20)
  - BIOLOGY PROF. PART OF TEAM IN INDIA. (Box Box 20)
  - PATRIOT CLUB OUTDOOR MARKETS. (Box Box 20)
  - "PROGOFF" JOURNAL WRITING WORKSHOP. (Box Box 20)
  - FENWICK LIBRARY RECEIVES FUMIGATION CHAMBER. (Box Box 20)
  - ROMANCE IN POPULAR LITERATURE LOVE AMONG VEGETABLES. (Box Box 20)
  - ALUMNI ANNUAL AWARDS RECIPIENT ANNOUNCED. (Box Box 20)
  - GMU GOES GERMAN. (Box Box 20)
  - TRAVEL TO GREECE FOR CREDIT. (Box Box 20)
  - GMU HONORED BY CANADIAN GOVERNMENT. (Box Box 20)
  - (Box Box 20)
  - WRITER TALKS ON NORTHERN IRELAND. (Box Box 20)
  - ELIJAN. (Box Box 20)
  - NATIONAL MERIT SEMI - FINALISTS. (Box Box 20)
  - GMU BUILDS PARTNERSHIP WITH INDUSTRIES. (Box Box 20)
  - JUAN MONTALVO. (Box Box 20)
  - JAZZ TAP ENSEMBLE. (Box Box 20)
  - AMERICAN RIGHTS SUBJECT - GM - LECTURE - DICK. (Box Box 20)
  - FOREIGN FILMS FOR NOVA. (Box Box 20)
  - "OUTDOOR DANCE FESTIVAL". (Box Box 20)
  - STATEWIDE COUNCIL OF VISITORS. (Box Box 20)
  - GMU VIETNAMESE PROF. ELECTED TO OFFICES. (Box Box 20)
  - FIRST ORIENTATION SCHEDULED AT GMU. (Box Box 20)
  - "UNIVERSITY DAY" (SERVICES AWARDS ACTIVITIES). (Box Box 20)
  - SOVIET & AMERICAN DEBATE. (Box Box 20)
  - TUITION & FEES INCREASE. (Box Box 20)
  - RIORDAN APPOINTED ADMISSIONS DIRECTOR. (Box Box 20)
  - MARKET YOUR MBA. (Box Box 20)
  - MEDICAL ETHICS SEMINAR. (Box Box 20)
  - MEDICINE & LAW. (Box Box 20)
  - IRISH FESTIVAL. (Box Box 20)
  - REGIONAL SEMINAR ON JAPAN. (Box Box 20)
  - DICK GREGORY SPEAKS. (Box Box 20)
  - HEALTH FAIR 82. (Box Box 20)
  - FATHER DRINAN ADDRESSES HUMAN RIGHTS AT GMU. (Box Box 20)
  - FRENCH LITERATURE ON LOCATION. (Box Box 20)
  - ROLE OF CABINET OFFICER DISCUSSED AT GMU. (Box Box 20)
  - REFRESHER COURSE FOR NURSES. (Box Box 20)
  - SPRING LITERARY SYMPOSIUM. (Box Box 20)
  - THE LEGACY OF GEORGE MASON. (Box Box 20)
  - GMU NURSING CONT. ED. PROGRAM APPRAISAL. (Box Box 20)
  - GMU BOARD OF VISITORS NOMINEE SOUGHT. (Box Box 20)
  - GMU PROFESSORS AWARDED FELLOWSHIP. (Box Box 20)
  - EFFECTS OF COMPUTERS ON SOCIETY FAC. LECTURE SERIES. (Box Box 20)
  - GOVERNMENT CONTRACT SEMINAR. (Box Box 20)
  - EDUCATION CONFERENCE. (Box Box 20)
  - MUSIC SYMPOSIUM FOR HIGH SCHOOL GROUP. (Box Box 20)
  - ALUMNI REUNIONS. (Box Box 20)
  - NAT. JR. VARSITY DEBATE TOURNAMENT. (Box Box 20)
  - CHAMBER MUSIC ENSEMBLE AT RE. LEE. BOYHOOD HOME. (Box Box 20)
  - STUDY TOUR OF EGYPT PHARAOH'S LANDS. (Box Box 20)
  - POWER OUT ! FLASH. (Box Box 20)
  - FACULTY RECITAL. (Box Box 20)
  - ANNUAL PHONATHON. (Box Box 20)
  - A. TOMBES ELECTED TO CONSORTIUM. (Box Box 20)
  - GLORIANNA SINGERS AT GMU. (Box Box 20)
  - BUDDISM DISCUSSED AT GMU. (Box Box 20)
  - GMU NURSING DEPARTMENT OFFERS A COURSE ON IMMUNOPATHOLOGY /M.L./C.I (Box Box 21)
  - AUTHOR ALEX HALEY AND DR. MARY FRANCES PERRY FEATURED SPEAKERS DURING GMU'S BLACK HISTORY MONTH CELEBRATION /M. LESANE /P.R. (Box Box 21)
  - GREAT DECISIONS /P.J. GOODMAN P.R. AND P.S.A / (Box Box 21)
  - GMU OFFERS NURSING REFRESHER COURSE / CALENDER ITEM /M. LESANE. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU ECONOMIST APPOINTED DISTINGUISHED FELLOW /H. ACKERMAN /N.R. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU PRESENTS FREE LECTURE ON CONTEMPORARY JAPANESE THEATER /N.R. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU PRESENTS FREE LECTURE ON CONTEMPORARY JAPANESE THEATRE /N.R. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU HOLDS MUSIC AUDITIONS / MICHELLE LESANE /P.S.A. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU SPONSORS HOST FAMILY PROGRAM/P.S.A /P.J. GOODMAN. (Box Box 21)
  - TOM DUNN HOLDS SEMINAR AT GMU. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU TAKES MAJOR STEPS TO SUPPORT HIGH TECHNOLOGY /HELEN A./N.R. (Box Box 21)
  - NO ELECTRICITY ON CAMPUS TUESDAY MORNING /FLASH / PENNY GOODMAN. (Box Box 21)
  - TUSCAN WRITER WINS NATIONAL AWARD/JOAN ZIEMBA /N.R. & CUTLINE. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU PROFESSOR STUDIES WASH RISK ESTABLISHMENT /NR/ PAULA ODIN. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU FACULTY EXPLORES THE SECRETE OF AGAIN /NR/ M. LESANE. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU HOSTS MINORITY STUDENTS. (Box Box 21)
  - IMPROVED BUSINESS WRITING GOAL. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU LAW SCHOOL PLANS SEMINAR ON EMPLOYMENT OF THE HANDICAPPED /P.G. (Box Box 21)
  - GEORGE MASON UNIVERSITY DEBATES THE ISSUE /M. LESANE. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU ALUMNI NIGHT BASKETBALL GAME/ CALENDER ITEM / PENNY GOODMAN. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU ALUMNI NIGHT BASKETBALL/ P.S.A /PENNY GOODMAN. (Box Box 21)
  - READ ALL ABOUT IT IN G.M. ACADEMIC JOURNALS /PAULA ODIN /N.R. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU PUBLISHES MEMORIES OF LOCAL BUSINESS ENTREPRENEUR / PAULA ODIN /N.R. (Box Box 21)
  - LISTING FOR FEBRUARY LITERARY CALENDER /JOAN ZIEMBA /CALENDER ITEM. (Box Box 21)
  - CLAY CLASSES FOR CHILDREN - HELEN ACKERMAN / CALENDER ITEM. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU OFFERS TOUR TO SOVIET UNION / H. ACKERMAN /N.R. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU GLORIANA SINGERS TO PERFORM CALENDER ITEM /M. LESANE / 1-17-84. (Box Box 21)
  - OPEN HOUSE FOR MINORITY STUDENTS. (Box Box 21)
  - HOLIDAYS CONCERTS JAZZ ENSEMBLE, CHAMBER ORCHESTRA, SYMPHONIC WINDS. (Box Box 21)
  - CONFERENCE ON SMALL BUSINESS INNOVATION RESEARCH. (Box Box 21)
  - WINNERS IN VIENNA ART SOCIETY EXHIBIT. (Box Box 21)
  - ALEX HALEY AT GMU. (Box Box 21)
  - GLENN SMITH COMPOSES INSPIRATIONAL MUSIC. (Box Box 21)
  - NURSING BOARDS EXAMINATION. (Box Box 21)
  - LOCAL HOMEMAKER AND STUDENT WINS COMPUTER /PENNY GOODMAN. (Box Box 21)
  - GREAT DECISIONS '84 HELD AT GEORGE MASON UNIVERSITY / PENNY GOODMAN. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU STUDENTS SHARE NATIONAL WRITING AWARD / PENNY GOODMAN. (Box Box 21)
  - MU. LAW PROFESSOR TACKLES HEALTH. (Box Box 21)
  - DANCE AUDITION. (Box Box 21)
  - ANNANDALE RESIDENT HONORED FOR ACADEMIC ACHIEVEMENT AT GMU/ N.V./F.J. (Box Box 21)
  - HERNDON RESIDENT HONORED FOR ACADEMIC ACHIEVEMENT AT GMU / N.R./P.J (Box Box 21)
  - GMU DANCE PROF. LAUNCHES DANCE CO. IN WASH. CONCERT. (Box Box 21)
  - INTERNATIONAL AWARENESS SERIES. (Box Box 21)
  - SYMPHONIC WINDS. (Box Box 21)
  - SYMPHONIC CHORUS - BRAHMS CONCERT. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU NOVICE FORENSICS COMPETITION. (Box Box 21)
  - HAZEL, VOLUNTEER OF THE YEAR. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU'S DOCTOR OF ARTS PROGRAM. (Box Box 21)
  - GEN. APPOINTED TO BOARD VISITORS. (Box Box 21)
  - FROM FAIRY TALE TO SUPER HERO. (Box Box 21)
  - FRENCH HISTORIAN TO DISCUSS REAGAN AND MITTERAND. (Box Box 21)
  - FOREIGN FILM FESTIVAL. (Box Box 21)
  - HOST AN INTERNATIONAL STUDENT. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU PROGRAM RECEIVES CALCULATOR DONATION. (Box Box 21)
  - IMMIGRATION LAW SEMINAR. (Box Box 21)
  - OLIN FOUNDATION CHAIR AWARDED TO WALTER WILLIAMS. (Box Box 21)
  - POTTERY INSTRUCTION & OPEN STUDIO. (Box Box 21)
  - DANCE CO. ANNUAL FALL CONCERT. FLASH - UNLIGHTED PATHWAYS. (Box Box 21)
  - ANNUAL CHRISTMAS FANFARE CONCERT. (Box Box 21)
  - CHRISTMAS CRAFT FAIR (Box Box 21)
  - PUBLIC INVITED TO GRADUATE ABD PROFESSIONAL SCHOOL DAYS. (Box Box 21)
  - LANDSCAPE PAINTING BY CHINESE ARTISTS. (Box Box 21)
  - F. LEE BAILEY TO APPEAR AT LAW SCHOOL. (Box Box 21)
  - CROSS COUNTY REGISTRATION. (Box Box 21)
  - NEW RECTOR AND FIRST STUDENT JOIN BD. OF VISITORS. (Box Box 21)
  - HOT L. BALTIMORE. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU FORENSICS TEAM ELECTS CO - CAPTAIN. (Box Box 21)
  - FIRST STUDENT SEAT ON GMU BOARD OF VISITORS. (Box Box 21)
  - WATERCOLOR EXHIBIT - EAST COAST SCENES, MARLIN FENICAL. (Box Box 21)
  - EDUCATION '83 CONFERENCE. (Box Box 21)
  - COMPUTER TECHNOLOGY NURSING WORKSHOP. (Box Box 21)
  - "WHAT'S NEW IN AGING WORKSHOP". (Box Box 21)
  - WORKSHOP ON GENEALOGY. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU CELEBRATES 10 YEARS OF COMMITMENT TO ADULT LEARNING. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU SPONSORS LECTURE ON SUPER COMPUTERS NURSING CONT. ED WORKSHOP. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU NURSING CONTINUING EDUCATION HOLDS WRITING WORKSHOP. (Box Box 21)
  - PROGOFF JOURNAL WRITING WORKSHOP SCHEDULED AT GMU. (Box Box 21)
  - LOCAL STUDENTS PERFORM WITH GEORGE MASON SYMPHONIC WINDS. (Box Box 21)
  - "VISUAL POETRY" EXHIBIT ON DISPLAY AT GMU. (Box Box 21)
  - POTTERY CLASSES OFFERED AT GMU. (Box Box 21)
  - PROGRAM - ARTS EXPLOSION. (Box Box 21)
  - ARMY BLUE PLAY BIG BAND. (Box Box 21)
  - MUSIC, THEATER, DANCE & ARTS. (Box Box 21)
  - FACULTY SHOWCASE. (Box Box 21)
  - GENERAL. (Box Box 21)
  - GOSPEL MUSIC. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU FACULTY'S CONCERT. (Box Box 21)
  - GENERAL, CUTLINE. (Box Box 21)
  - EDITORIAL, FX. JOUR. (Box Box 21)
  - PHILLIPS COLLECTION - SENT TO UPI AND AP. (Box Box 21)
  - 2MD MUSIC, DANCE THEATER, DANCE AND ARTS. (Box Box 21)
  - SELDOM SCENE. (Box Box 21)
  - GEORGE MASON ARTS EXPLOSION EVENTS FOR WEEK OF OCT. 27TH TO NOV. 2. (Box Box 21)
  - CANADIAN LATIN AMERICAN MUSIC, CAROLYN DILL. CANADIAN PIANIST. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU BEGINS ITS SECOND BIG WEEK OF ARTS CELEBRATIONS. (Box Box 21)
  - MOVING ART MAKES ITS WAY TO GMU. (Box Box 21)
  - DIALOGUE ON U.S. AND CANADIAN ART. (Box Box 21)
  - EVENTS FOR THE WEEK OF NOVEMBER 3-9. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU CELEBRATES THE ARTS WITH A MONTH OF EVENTS. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU RECEIVES GIFTS OF READING MACHINE. (Box Box 21)
  - INTERSTATE VAN LINES SCHOLARSHIP ESTABLISHED. (Box Box 21)
  - FORMER FIRST LADY OF VA AWARD GRANT TO GMU. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU APPOINTS ELLAMAE DOYLE. (Box Box 21)
  - REFRESHER COURSE FOR REGISTERED NURSES. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU SPONSORS COLLEGE ORIENTATION PROGRAM. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU SITE OF FOURTH ELDER HOSTEL PROGRAM. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU/FAIRFAX COUNTY COORDINATE ORFT SCHULWERK MUSIC TEACHING. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU CELEBRATES THE ARTS WITH A MONTH OF ACTIVITIES. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU SPONSORS PILOT SKILL BUILDING PROGRAM. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU PLAYERS PRESENT "THE PLAYWRIGHT". (Box Box 21)
  - FINAL OUTDOOR MARKET OF SEASON AT GMU. (Box Box 21)
  - AUDITIONS FOR MUSICAL GROUPS. (Box Box 21)
  - NURSING REFRESHER COURSE. (Box Box 21)
  - CHANGES GREET STUDENT RETURNING TO GMU. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU OFFERS MANAGEMENT COURSE FOR NURSES. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU SPONSORS EXERCISE PROGRAM FOR OLDER ADULTS. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU COMPOSER'S WORK TO BE PERFORMED BY NAT'L SYMPHONY. (Box Box 21)
  - VIRGINIA ACADEMY OF SCIENCE HOLDS 61ST ANNUAL MEETING AT GMU. (Box Box 21)
  - WEEL RADIO STATION. (Box Box 21)
  - INDUSTRY, LABOR, GOVERNMENT DISCUSS HIGH TECHNOLOGY AT GMU. (Box Box 21)
  - STILL IN TOP TEN GMU FORENSICS TEAM. (Box Box 21)
  - CULTURE EXPLODES AT GMU. (Box Box 21)
  - POWER OUT! (Box Box 21)
  - GEORGE MASON AWARDS FIRST DOCTORAL DEGREE. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU ANNOUNCES AUDITIONS FOR SUMMER MUSICAL ENSEMBLES. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU BUSINESS HONOR SOCIETY DONATES MONEY FOR COMPUTER LOUNGE. (Box Box 21)
  - BLACK ORGANIZATION DONATES JOURNALS TO GMU. (Box Box 21)
  - GEORGE MASON HOLDS DANCE AUDITIONS FOR PROSPECTIVE STUDENTS. (Box Box 21)
  - MORE THAN 2000 STUDENTS GRADUATE AT GMU COMMENCEMENT. (Box Box 21)
  - ATTENTION STUDENTS CLOSING "A" LOT. (Box Box 21)
  - SUMMER CAMP FOCUSES ON FITNESS AND COMPUTERS. (Box Box 21)
  - "ON GUARD AGAINST THEFT". (Box Box 21)
  - CLAY PLAY FOR KIDS. (Box Box 21)
  - BLACK FRATERNITY AWARDS SCHOLARSHIPS TO GMU. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU COORDINATOR RECEIVES AWARD FOR LOGISTICS PROGRAM. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU DANCE DEPARTMENT TP PRESENT SHOWING OF WORKS 388140. (Box Box 21)
  - SOVIET DIPLOMAT DISCUSSES NUCLEAR WAR AT GMU 388140. (Box Box 21)
  - PIANIST LEE SUMMER TO PERFORM WITH GMU ORCHESTRA. (Box Box 21)
  - ENVIRONMENTAL EXPERTS GATHER AT GMU FOR EARTH SYMPOSIUM. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU OFFERS NURSING STATE BOARD REVIEW COURSE. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU PRESENTS FREE THEATRE FESTIVAL. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU CENTER FOR HEALTH PROMO. SENIOR FITNESS WORKSHOP. (Box Box 21)
  - MANAGEMENT CONFERENCE TO BE HELD AT GEORGE MASON. (Box Box 21)
  - ACCLAIMED IRISH POET SEAMUS HEANEY AT GMU. (Box Box 21)
  - REVOLUTIONARY UNDERGRADUATE PROGRAM OPENS TO FRESHMEN PAGE. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU STUDENTS RECEIVE AWARDS FOR ACADEMMIC EXCELLENCE. (Box Box 21)
  - OUTDOOR MARKET SEASON BEGINS AT GMU. (Box Box 21)
  - NEA'S WALTER ANDERSON KEYNOTES GMU ANNUAL ALUMNI BANQUET. (Box Box 21)
  - CAPITAL WOODWIND QUINTET TO CLOSE OUT SPRING CONCERT SERIES. (Box Box 21)
  - GEORGE MASON ALUMNI BANQUET PSA. (Box Box 21)
  - GOVERNOR ROBB TO SPEAK AT GMU GRADUATION. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU THEATRE PRESENTS VANITIES AS FINAL PRODUCTION OF SEASON. (Box Box 21)
  - F.T.P POSTERS ON EXHIBIT AT FENWICK LIBRARY. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU SPARS AT BRITISH INTERNATIONAL DEBATE JOURNEY. (Box Box 21)
  - AUTHOR RONALD SUKENECK AT GMU. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU TO HOST NOVELIST FREDERICK BUSCH. (Box Box 21)
  - SEMINAR ON "HUMAN SEXUALITY - NATURE OR NURTURE". (Box Box 21)
  - GMU HOSTS HISTORY DAY. (Box Box 21)
  - SPORTS AND FITNESS GALA AT ROBINSON HIGH SCHOOL. (Box Box 21)
  - CHARD ALLEN LECTURE AT GMU. (Box Box 21)
  - IS AMERICA FAILING ITS ALLIES? (Box Box 21)
  - GMU THEATRE PRESENTS COMEDY HIT VANITIES. (Box Box 21)
  - GEORGE MASON UNIVERSITY DANCE CO. PERFORMS AT KENNEDY CENTER. (Box Box 21)
  - HEP EXERCISE PROGRAM FOR OLDER ADULTS AT GMU. (Box Box 21)
  - ART IN PUBLIC PLACES PROJECT. (Box Box 21)
  - DANCER SENTA DRIVER ARRIVES AT GMU. (Box Box 21)
  - CONFLICT MANAGEMENT WORKSHOP FOR NURSES. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU SYMPHONIC WINDS PERFORM IN CONCERT. (Box Box 21)
  - IRISH POET GALWAY KINNELL AT GMU. 384140 (Box Box 21)
  - ZIP CODE PARTY FOR GMU ALUMNI C.I. 385140 (Box Box 21)
  - GMU DANCE COMPANY TO PRESENT SPRING CONCERT. 388140 (Box Box 21)
  - ART ON WHEELS VA MUSEUM. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU HOSTS PHYSICS CONTEST. (Box Box 21)
  - TUITION HIKE. (Box Box 21)
  - JOB FAIR. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU HOSTS NOVELIST ANN BEATTIE. (Box Box 21)
  - FREE MUSIC CLINICS - BRASS QUINTET. (Box Box 21)
  - ALUMNI GOLF OUTING. (Box Box 21)
  - ARTHUR PETERSEN STAR OF *SOAP* AT GMU. (Box Box 21)
  - VOLUNTEERS NEEDED AT FENWICK LIBRARY. (Box Box 21)
  - TOURING GREECE. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU CELEBRATES INTERNATIONAL WEEK. (Box Box 21)
  - HANDEL'S ISRAEL PERFORMED AT GMU. (Box Box 21)
  - CONSULTANT TO THE PRESIDENT APPOINTED TO GMU. (Box Box 21)
  - REGISTRATION OPEN FOR GMU'S PRESCHOOL PROGRAM. (Box Box 21)
  - DAY OF CELEBRATION FOR GMU. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU FOR NAT'L REGIONAL CLINIC ON PHY. FITNESS & SPORTS. (Box Box 21)
  - NAT'L ASSOC. HOLDS CONF. ON VIETNAMESE AMERICAN EDUCATION. (Box Box 21)
  - BIOLOGY ISSUES DISCUSSED AT GMU. (Box Box 21)
  - MALAYSIA AMBASSADOR TO SPEAK AT GMU. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU STUDENT NURSE ASSOC. HOLDS ANNUAL HEALTH FAIR. (Box Box 21)
  - WASH SAXOPHONE QUARTET PERFORMS AT GMU AND HOLDS MASTER CLASS. (Box Box 21)
  - NURSING QUALITY CIRCLES WORKSHOP HELD AT GMU. (Box Box 21)
  - POET ALAN GINSBERG. (Box Box 21)
  - POET RRALD STERN. (Box Box 21)
  - ROGER WILKINS (BLACK HISTORY MONTH). (Box Box 21)
  - REFRESHER COURSE FOR REGISTERED NURSES. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU STUDENT WHO'S WHO 1983. (Box Box 21)
  - ANDREW YOUNG TO SPEND AT GMU. (Box Box 21)
  - WEEL RATIO STATION DONATED TO GMU. (Box Box 21)
  - GLORIANA SINGERS AT KENNEDY CENTER. (Box Box 21)
  - GLORIANA SINGERS AT VIRGINIA MUSEUMS. (Box Box 21)
  - SPRING CLASSICAL MUSIC SERIES. (Box Box 21)
  - JENNIFER RUGEL - YOUNG WOMAN AMERICA. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU SPOTLIGHTS CULTURE. (Box Box 21)
  - FREDERICK DOUGLASS STAGE. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU OFFERS TOUR TO SOVIET UNION. (Box Box 21)
  - MAY CALENDER OF EVENTS - PERFORMING ARTS. (Box Box 21)
  - WORK THAT BODY. (Box Box 21)
  - FORENSICS - AND SPEAKING OF .... (Box Box 21)
  - ELIZABETH MURK STEVENS. (Box Box 21)
  - FTP - TWO PLAYS AT GMU. (Box Box 21)
  - BICULTURALISM WORKSHOP - NURSING. (Box Box 21)
  - ALUMNI AWARDS BANQUET. (Box Box 21)
  - ALUMNI ASSOCIATION SEEKS NOMINATIONS. (Box Box 21)
  - 1983 PHONATHON. (Box Box 21)
  - THE LEGACY OF GMU. (Box Box 21)
  - DR. PELHAM - OUTSTANDING WOMAN OF YEAR. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU PRESENTS PAST - CONCERT. (Box Box 21)
  - ART FACULTY EXHIBIT WORKS. (Box Box 21)
  - THREE ENGLISH FACULTY CAPTURE NEA GRANTS. (Box Box 21)
  - CONFLICT MANAGEMENT SYMPOSIUM. (Box Box 21)
  - COURSE ON NUCLEAR WAR. (Box Box 21)
  - WILLIAM STYRON - GUEST LECTURE. (Box Box 21)
  - ALUMNI PRE - GAME RECEPTION. (Box Box 21)
  - CENTER CONFLICT RESOLUTION AWARDED GRANTS. (Box Box 21)
  - FORENSICS TEAM FOCUSES ON "ORAL GALLERY OF ART". (Box Box 21)
  - FINANCIAL AID AWARENESS WORKSHOP. (Box Box 21)
  - EXHIBIT STUDENT ART WORKS, METRO GALLERY. (Box Box 21)
  - PAST C.K. WILLIAMS AT GMU. (Box Box 21)
  - SCULPTURES FROM NATIONAL GALLERY OF ART. (Box Box 21)
  - ANDREW YOUNG TO SPEAK AT BLACK HISTORY MONTH. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU COMPLETES SELF - ASSESSMENT. (Box Box 21)
  - NEW BIOLOGY COLLECTION AT GMU FENWICK LIBRARY. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU HOSTS WRITER FORENSICS JOURNEY. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU PERFORMS CHAMBER MUSIC - 19TH CENTURY GERMAN. (Box Box 21)
  - GMU HOLDS OPEN CHORAL / ORCHESTRA READING FOR COMMUNITY. (Box Box 21)
  - LIBRARY SKILL WORKSHOP. (Box Box 21)
  - AUDIENCE - COUNSELING CONFERENCE. (Box Box 21)
  - MARKETS FOR FICTION DISCUSSION. (Box Box 21)
  - WM. WILSON'S "DEEP SOUTH" EXHIBIT. (Box Box 21)
  - EUGENE ODUM TO SPEAK AT GMU. (Box Box 22)
  - DR. S. FRED SINGER TO TEACH COURSE AT GMU. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU THEATRE COMPANY PRESENTS. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU TO SPONSOR OPEN HOUSE ON DECEMBER 2. (Box Box 22)
  - STUDENTS AWARDS. (Box Box 22)
  - PERFORMING ARTS EVENTS 1985 (Box Box 22)
  - WASHINGTON OPERA STARS. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU STRENGTHENS TEACHER PREPARATION PROGRAM. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU OFFER STATE BOARD REVIEW COURSE. (Box Box 22)
  - BLACK HISTORY MONTH. (Box Box 22)
  - WASHINGTON OPERA STARS. (Box Box 22)
  - FAIRFAX LIBRARY PRESENTS GMU IN RECITAL. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU HOLDS DANCE AUDITION. (Box Box 22)
  - REMOVAL OF LEAVES. (Box Box 22)
  - VIOLINIST BENNY KIM IN CONCERT. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU NURSING SPRING LINE - UP. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU LAW SCHOOL ALUMNI PRESENTS ART AUCTION, H. ACKERMAN. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU PRESENTS FALL DANCE CONCERT M. LESANE N.R, C.I. P.S.A. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU HOLDS TRAUMA WORKSHOP FOR NURSES M. LESANE. N.R, P.S.A. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU PROFESSOR WINS NATIONAL ESSAY COMPETITION A. ALLMAN/ N.R. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU RECEIVES ENERGY GRANT M. LESANE N.R. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU OPEN HOUSE F. MOSHOS N.R, C.I. P.S.A. (Box Box 22)
  - GRAD ENGINEERING OPEN HOUSE F. MOSHOS N.R, C.I. P.S.A. (Box Box 22)
  - COMPUTER SEMINARS. (Box Box 22)
  - ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE H. ACKERMAN N.R. C.I. (Box Box 22)
  - QUILT INFORMATION H. ACKERMAN N.R. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU ALUMNI HOME COMING F. MOSHOS. C.I. (Box Box 22)
  - OLD VIC PERFORMS AT GMU M. LESANE C.I, P.S.A. (Box Box 22)
  - BREEZEWAY REPAIR F. MOSHOS I.H.F. (Box Box 22)
  - DR. RUTH WESTHEIMER TO SPEAK F. MOSHOS AT GMU. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU TO HOLD PUBLIC HEARING ON SELECTION OF BOOKS F. MOSHOS. M.A. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU PROFESSOR TO SPEAK ON DANGER OF NUCLEAR WAR. (Box Box 22)
  - CHRISTMAS CRAFTS SHOW AT GMU A. ALLMAN. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU LIBRARY RECEIVES AFRICAN ARTIFACTS. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU'S HOLIDAY SEASON OF MUSIC AND THEATRE. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU FOUNDATION RECEIVES GRANT FROM AFCEA, A. ALLMAN. (Box Box 22)
  - INTERNATIONAL ARTS FESTIVAL LISTING, M. LESANE. (Box Box 22)
  - AUTHOR JOHN EDGAR WIDEMAN SPEAKS AT GMU, J. ZIEMBA. (Box Box 22)
  - PIANISTS JEAN CARRINGTON COOK TO GIVE BENEFIT AT GMU, M. LESANE. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU PRESENTS FREE CONCERTS M. LESANE N.R (Box Box 22)
  - CORPORATE ART COMES FROM BEHIND P.S.A, C.I. CLOSED DOORS, M. LESANE. (Box Box 22)
  - TRIO DELL' ARTE PERFORMS AT GMU, M. LESANE C.L N.R, P.S.A. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU RECEIVES GIFT OF ART BOOKS, A. ALLMAN. (Box Box 22)
  - NOTED LINGUIST, NOAM CHOMSKY TP SPEAK AT GMU, F. MOSHOS. C.I, N.R. M.A. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU STUDENTS RECEIVE SCHOLARSHIPS, A, ALLMAN. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU WRITER'S CLUB HOST PANEL ON WRITING AS A PROF., J. ZIEMBA. (Box Box 22)
  - LINKING MGT. SUPPORT SYSTEM TO STRATEGIC BUS. PLAN. HELEN. (Box Box 22)
  - ARGENTINE AUTHOR JORGE LUIS TO SPEAK AT GMU, C. HILL. (Box Box 22)
  - PROTECTING SOFTWARE DISCUSSED AT GMU, H. ACKERMAN. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU PRESENTS A TRIBUTE TO C. HILL., SPANISH POET LEON FELIPE. M.A. (Box Box 22)
  - TRADITIONAL VIETNAMESE MUSIC PERFORMED AT GMU. (Box Box 22)
  - GMU OPENS ART SEASON WITH FACULTY EXHIBIT. (Box Box 22)
  - FAIRFAX HIGH STUDENTS WIN SUMMER JOBS AT MELPAR E SYSTEMS. (Box Box 22)
  - FOLGER THEATRE MUSICAL GROUP PERFORMS W/ GEORGE MASON UNIVERSITY C.I. M. LESANE. (Box Box 22)
  - THE TWELVE NIGHT P.S.A. C.I. M. LESANE. (Box Box 22)
  - UPCOMING EVENTS AT GMU, 1984 - 1985 C.I. M. LESANE AUGUST 31, 1984. (Box Box 22)
  - SYMPOSIUM RELIGION AND POLITICS, CANDACE HILL. (Box Box 22)